[
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47]?",
      "correctAnswer": "44",
      "options": [
        "43",
        "44",
        "45",
        "46"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47, 48]?",
      "correctAnswer": "45",
      "options": [
        "44",
        "45",
        "46",
        "47"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [43, 44, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49]?",
      "correctAnswer": "46",
      "options": [
        "45",
        "46",
        "47",
        "48"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [44, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49, 50]?",
      "correctAnswer": "47",
      "options": [
        "46",
        "47",
        "48",
        "49"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [45, 46, 47, 48, 49, 50, 51]?",
      "correctAnswer": "48",
      "options": [
        "47",
        "48",
        "49",
        "50"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [46, 47, 48, 49, 50, 51, 52]?",
      "correctAnswer": "49",
      "options": [
        "48",
        "49",
        "50",
        "51"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [47, 48, 49, 50, 51, 52, 53]?",
      "correctAnswer": "50",
      "options": [
        "49",
        "50",
        "51",
        "52"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [48, 49, 50, 51, 52, 53, 54]?",
      "correctAnswer": "51",
      "options": [
        "50",
        "51",
        "52",
        "53"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [49, 50, 51, 52, 53, 54, 55]?",
      "correctAnswer": "52",
      "options": [
        "51",
        "52",
        "53",
        "54"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [50, 51, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56]?",
      "correctAnswer": "53",
      "options": [
        "52",
        "53",
        "54",
        "55"
      ]
    }
]